Now this lecture going to look at another Amazon
bedrock capability called as bedrock prompt management.
Amazon bedrock prompt management
simplifies the creation evaluation,
versioning, and sharing of prompt
to get better response from the foundation models.
So in summary, Amazon bedrock prompt management
allows you to create prompt templates, evaluate them,
do the versioning, and then share
those prompts across the organization.
Now let's try and understand how you can use
prompt template through an example.
So this is our Gen A powered equipment SME assistant,
where the winter bind field technician
sends the incident report and images.
And then we have the equipment SME at a global location
who further sends this incident report and images
and asks the foundation model to summarize
the equipment logs.
So let's assume that these are the log details
and it has asked the foundation model to summarize.
Now if we go back, what is our user prompt?
Equipment log details and summarize.
Now if we send these details to the foundation model,
we know we're not going to get great results
because we're not providing any context.
So that's wherein the concept of system prompts
come into play.
So along with this user prompt, what we can send
to the foundation model is, you are a wind turbine
subject matter expert specializing
in equipment analysis and log based troubleshooting.
So it gives foundation model some context on the persona
it needs to act as to respond to this user prompt.
Then we can additionally say produce a concise one-page summary
and highlight the key anomalies and failure patterns.
So now we have the user prompt and we have the system prompt.
So now together user prompt and system prompts,
we're going to send to the Amazon bedrock.
So it has the full context and the response
that we might get here is going to be much better
than just sending the user prompt.
Now how does Amazon bedrock prompt management
help in this scenario?
So what you can do with the prompt managed capability
is create these system prompts.
So you create the system prompts in the prompt management
then you evaluate them, you version them,
then you can share these prompts across the organization.
OK, that's pretty much it from this lecture.
I'll see in the next lecture.
Thank you.